Hello, everyone. 'Welcome to Clínica por el Mundo', a website that is a health encyclopaedia
and aims to be as accessible and user-friendly as possible. We have various
forms, such as the contact form and the search engine, which can be used to make different queries.
We can also return to the home page using the breadcrumb trail, but we will look at that later.
We also have a place to meet the creators, who are Alex Daniel Apolo and myself,
Francisco José. As we said, thanks to the breadcrumb map, we can move around the site more easily.
A site map allows us to see a summary of all the options available and access them from here,
such as the home page, ‘About us’ or the search engine. Then we
have a series of features, such as Disease of the Day, where we can see a disease with an image,
symptoms, treatment and a related video. In addition to that, we have tables such as, for example,
a comparison of health insurance prices, with colours that comply with the appropriate standards.
There is also an alphabetical search engine, where you can enter the letter ‘A’, for example,
and although you can move on to the following letters, you can also access diseases
that begin with that letter, such as bronchitis under ‘B’,
where you will find a description, symptoms, treatment and related videos. If we go to Treatment, for example,
it allows us to access videos of the previously selected disease more quickly.
We also have videos on the home page with a health theme,
and we can access diseases of the human body just by clicking
on the button with the picture of the body. These are the functions of our website.